import { QuestionAnswer } from "@/types/type";

export const questionsAndAnswers: QuestionAnswer[] = [
  { question: "A man's best friend", answer: "DOG" },
  { question: "A small feline animal", answer: "CAT" },
  { question: "A food item made from dough", answer: "BREAD" },
  { question: "Essential for hydration", answer: "WATER" },
  { question: "Yellow fruit that monkeys love", answer: "BANANA" },
  { question: "The red fruit often mistaken for a vegetable", answer: "TOMATO" },
  { question: "It shines in the sky during the day", answer: "SUN" },
  { question: "A flying mammal", answer: "BAT" },
  { question: "Used to write or draw", answer: "PENCIL" },
  { question: "The opposite of cold", answer: "HOT" },
  { question: "The largest land animal", answer: "ELEPHANT" },
  { question: "You read this to gain knowledge", answer: "BOOK" },
  { question: "Something you wear on your head", answer: "HAT" },
  { question: "You open this to enter a room", answer: "DOOR" },
  { question: "A vehicle that flies in the sky", answer: "PLANE" },
  { question: "A reptile that slithers", answer: "SNAKE" },
];
